Parin Thalangdee

Santa Ana, CA 92704 • Parin. Thalangdee@outlook.com • (818) 441-3879 • Online Portfolio

Summary

Full stack developer with 1 year of personal experience in Javascript, CSS, and HTML. Completed University of California Irvine's immersive coding camp with a grade of 94% where I learned fundamentals of MySQL and the MERN stack. Constant improvement has been my theme by self starting personal projects that take advantage of the new skills I learned and honing skills I had prior. My relentless pursuit of knowledge has helped me in my past career and has been an asset in pivoting into Web Development.

Technical Skills

- JavaScript
- HTML5
- MongoDB
- CSS3
- React.js

- Node.js
- Express.js
- JQuery
- SQL
- MySQL Server

- VS Code
- Insomnia
- MongoDB Atlas
- MongoDB Compass
- Windows & MacOS

Experience

Velocity Motoring Product Specialist

Anaheim, CA

Oct 2020 – Mar 2022

- Influenced product releases by researching market trends which were then reported to product designers
- Identified user issues, notated their details, and reported common issues to product designers.
- Managed customer expectations by inquiring their application and intended uses to make expert recommendations.

Transamerican Auto Parts

Compton, CA

Product Specialist & After-sales Support

June 2016 – Feb 2020

- Committed product composition to memory of over 50 product kits and their applications.
- Reporting and communicating common issues to product designers and engineers.
- Abstract problem solving to dissect user commentary to troubleshoot a product and its interaction with their application.
- Served as technical expert at trade shows while acting as brand representative.

Supreme Suspension

La Mirada, CA

Technical Lead & Product Specialist

Jan 2013 – May 2016

- Led product specialist team by producing technical training and reference material.
- Communicating with the team about new products, product changes, and new hire training.
- Learned composition of over 40 products and their applications.
- Critical thinking used to interpret user data to produce reports for engineers.

- Send Foods:

An interactive food recipe sharing web app that allows users to upload their recipes and media content while being able to view submissions from other users.

- Coded in React.js, Material UI, Express.js, and MongoDB.
- Information is dynamically rendered in a responsive grid.

- PokeStats:

Data search and reference for trading card information. Users are able to search multiple datatypes to call server information to be rendered to the front end.

- Coded in Express.js, SQL, Javascript, and HTML
- Information is dynamically rendered in a responsive grid.

- Dinner with Schmucks:

Fun and interactive app that allows users to determine dinner, a drink with a fun quote to converse about. Using multiple API's, this app allows users to pick the character they would like to have a quote from then paired with a meal, recipe, and drink.

- Coded with JavaScript, CSS(Bootstrap), and HTML
- Fully responsive with multiple view windows.

Education

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA IRVINE, Div. of Continuing Education Full Stack Web Development (Grade 94%)

IRVINE, CA

August 2022

UNIVERSAL TECHNICAL INSTITUTE

Heavy Duty Diesel and Industrial Technology

RANCHO CUCAMONGA, CA

July 2012

Certificates

Coding Boot Camp Certificate University of California Irvine

August 2022